

#### Software Architect / Developer / Designer

# **Adam Lepley**

- □ adam@empathdesignllc.com
- Kenosha, WI
- linkedin.com/in/adam-lepley
- **%** (847) 505-9293

#### **Profile**

Software architect with +15 years of experience creating custom software solutions on a variety of platforms. I have a strong foundation in .Net development, but also very comfortable using low code solutions like PowerApps when appropriate.

More than development, my experience often enables me to lead development projects and help set the technological vision for my clients.

## **Primary Skills**

Net / C#DevOps / Github

XamarinAzure

WebAPIDocker

BlazorFigma / Stetch

WPFReact / Typescript

SQL / NoSqlo365 / SharePoint

MS Power Platform
 Dynamics / Dataverse

## **Project History**

## 2021 - Current Solution Architect & Development Lead @ Carnegie Hall

New York, NY

I architected and led the development of a newly created vaccine verification portal which Carnegie now uses to manage the vaccine verification process for performers and staff. This portal helped satisfy New York City and state requirements allowing it to reopen its doors for business ahead of schedule.

The solution consisted of a public facing intake form, which was built using .Net / Blazor, and stores that data temporarily in Azure Blob Storage during verification. Data workflows then migrate the results of the verification to a secured Dataverse instance where all events are managed

## 2021 - 2022 Solution Architect & Development Lead @ Thermo Fisher

Global

I architected and developed a solution which helps manage and organize supplier audits worldwide. This solution allows the end-end tracking of supplier audits and incorporates intelligence to help match qualified auditors.

The solutions was built on top of Microsoft's Office o365 and Power Platform leveraging Sharepoint, Power Apps and Power Automate.

## **Project History Cont.**

## 2021 - 2022 Solution Architect & Development Lead @ MOBILion Systems

Chadds Ford, PA

I helped designed, developed and deployed a Quality Management Portal built using SharePoint and PowerApps which help MOBILion System maintain procedure change records. This solution manages the entire change management lifecycle so that procedure revisions are centrally track, and send for collaboration and approved. This solution also schedules and tracks employee training when procedures are changed to help maintain ISO complience.

### 2016 - 2021 Mobile Solution Architect & Development Lead @ Wheels

Des Plaines, IL

This project was a long-term engagement in which I assisted Wheels in building their first public mobile app, which is available on the App Store and Google Play Store. The original goal of the application was to replace a web-based system used to track mileage and provide drivers with necessary documents. Over the years we add many new features, some of which include GPS tracking / stop detection, integration with emergency tow services, customer configured rental system and violation payments.

The application was built using Xamarin Forms with .Net Core web services running within Docker containers hosted on Azure and integrated with on-premise enterprise systems.

My original role on this project was to create a proof-of-concept mobile application that successfully integrated with their back-end infrastructure. That effort was successful and lead to muti-year engagement with many feature enhancements. I was responsible for the full stack architecture of the mobile solution and served as the lead developer on many new features.

#### 2010 – 2015 Senior Manager of Custom Development @ **Scientific Games**

Chicago, IL

Managed a team of developers (4-6) building internal application across a range of various business functions. The technical stack was primarily .Net which included C#, WPF, Silverlight, WinForms & Xamarin. My team often intergrated into other enterprise systems like Oracle and SAP and developed custom user interfaces that helped facilitate and automate business processes.

#### References

#### Alex Kassabov

PM @ DragonSpears

linkedin.com/in/alexkassabov

#### Norman Murrin

VP of Delivery @ Creospan linkedin.com/in/norman-murrin

## Mitch Cuter

Solutions Architect @ Netrix linkedin.com/in/mitch-cutler-04267512

## Mark Roden

Global Advisory Technology Director @ PwC

linkedin.com/in/markyroden

#### Alex Zakhodin

#### **Education**

2007 - 2011